http://www.jerkyusa.com/policies-and-information#36abe7cf-039b-457a-ae3b-683308d922b6

(620) 964-2222HomeShop JerkySpecialty ProductsAbout UsConvenience StoreSmokehousePolicies and InformationFAQ'sGalleryContactMoreHomeShop JerkySpecialty ProductsAbout UsConvenience StoreSmokehousePolicies and InformationFAQ'sGalleryContactHomeShop JerkySpecialty ProductsAbout UsGalleryContact
Fundraisers We offer a fund-raiser program for those looking to raise money for any organization (school, club, etc). Our first big fund-raiser was in November of 2008, when 27 boys of the Emporia Wrestling team made over $2200.00 in profit. Your group may sell as many flavors of jerky as you wish but we recommend starting out with our top 3 flavors, Mild, Hot and Teriyaki. We provide you with a copy of the order form and information you will need to get started. Just print off the amount of forms you need and start selling. When you are done, you can call, fax or email your totals in. We can either ship your orders (free shipping if your order is $500.00 or more) or you can pick them up at the factory. For more information, call toll free (800-322-0868) or send us an email.
Shipping Orders are shipped through USPS Priority Mail. Any order over $89.00 is free shipping, anything under that amount will have a standard fee of $9.99. If you place an order on Friday after 10:30 am CST through Tuesday morning before 10:30 am CST, your order will go out Tuesday morning. If you order after 11:00 am Tuesday but before 10:30 am on Wednesday, it will be shipped Wednesday morning. The same goes for the remainder of the week. Expect the shipment to arrive between one to four business days, depending on your location. Delivery areas include military addresses.Please contact us about International Orders.
Privacy PolicyThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for jerkyusa.com. This privacy noticeapplies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at anytime by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800-322-0868 or via email.
USDA CertifiedBBB Rating of A+Made in the USAMade in the USABBB Rating of A+Made in the USABBB Rating of A+BBB Rating of A+BBB Rating of A+
©2020 Luther's Smokehouse Inc. - All Rights Reserved.Website by Young GraphicsHomeShop JerkySpecialty ProductsConvenience StoreSmokehousePolicies and InformationFAQ'sGalleryContact
